Lucky Face Special Talk
Yay!
Well, but it's still amazing.
It's gorgeous, isn't it?
I'm so happy to see so many people here!
Live Chokoro Takamine no Nadeshiko!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Please, please, please, please.
Thank you very much.
Let's start by introducing ourselves one by one.
I'm Erisa Higashiyama.
I'm Himeri Komiyama.
I'm Momona Matsumoto.
I'm Sunao Kizuki
Yes, I am Suzumi Suzu.
Yes, I am Hina Hina.
Yes, I am Momoko Hashimoto.
Yes, I am Lili Harana.
Yes, I am Mikuru Hoshitani.
Yes, I am Sahara Hazuki.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Wow, wonderful. 10 people.
Ten people. Ten people.
Ten people. This may be the largest number of people interviewed in this distribution.
How was this interview?
How was it? It was a downpour at the Lucky Fest.
What did you think of it?
I was looking forward to performing for the first time, but it was too much of a downpour.
I was worried about the fans because it was pouring so hard.
But when we went to the rehearsal, the fans didn't even put on their kappas or anything.
We couldn't do it! It was raining! It was like, "It was raining!
I wanted to do my best to make the show as exciting as the rain,
It had stopped for a little while during the show, so we could see the faces of the fans and enjoyed the show.
Oh, I see. When the show started, it was amazing.
It was amazing.
It was amazing before it started, wasn't it?
What were you guys talking about? Oh my God.
Are we really doing this? Like, "This is impossible.
Are you saying, "This is impossible?
Well, tell them it's going to be sunny from now on.
Oh, there's such a thing as a sunny weather girl?
No, we've got two of them.
That's a little thin. Two out of ten?
Two out of ten?
What? Eight more rainbirds?
No, it's just...
We always have a pretty good chance of sunshine.
Rain was a bit of a bummer. It's been a while since we've had rain.
But I guess the two of us have helped weaken it a bit.
Weakened.
I'm glad.
Was it easy? Lucky festival. How was it? Everyone.
Yes, everyone shouted a lot,
And since we were allowed to take pictures of Nadeshiko Takamine, people were calling out to us while we were filming,
It was raining, but everyone's voices and energy were so powerful that we didn't feel it,
It was raining, but the energy of the audience was so strong that we felt like we wanted to be a part of the excitement,
We wanted to get excited together with the fans, and I think we were able to get excited together with them on stage.
Didn't you feel the rain?
Rain?
I'm really sorry, but the wind was blowing toward the fans, and it seemed like they were getting more of it than we were.
Really? Not many people came to the stage?
We had to go to the front.
They would see your bangs.
That's what he kept saying.
You don't want that, do you?
It's important. We're missing time.
It was like this, right? That's why.
I thought I didn't have bangs.
I did.
Thank you very much.
That's wonderful.
I saw the whole thing.
Thank you very much.
It was a lot of fun.
I knew it would be more exciting when I got wet,
I get excited when I get wet.
I understand.
It's when you don't want to get wet that the tension goes down the most.
The moment you give up, that's when the fans get excited.
The excitement of the fans when they've had enough.
Yes, it was great.
It was wonderful.
How about Nadeshiko?
Ibaraki is quite like this.
Do you have any connection with Ibaraki? Do you have any connections?
Wow....
Do you have any memories or impressions of Ibaraki?
Yes, it's very personal for me.
My guess is from Ibaraki.
I was at a Tower Records store in my hometown.
Whenever there was a pop-up event at the local Tower Records store
I would go to Ibaraki every time.
I would go to Ibaraki every time and try some of their specialties.
Your guess?
Yes, I did.
Who is your guess in Ibaraki? Takafumi Mito? Who?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Who's the house in Ibaraki?
I really like Yori Noguchi from Equal Love.
He's from Ibaraki.
I used to go there every time.
The Ibaraki people are so warm.
When I didn't know the way to get there, I would ask them.
I asked him if he had any good food.
They answered me warmly.
I have an image that the people of Ibaraki are very kind.
I have a great image of Ibaraki.
I guess you have to travel all the way to Ibaraki for your activities.
Yes.
I had to go to Ibaraki because there was a pop-up featuring my guess and it was only in my hometown, so I wanted to be there.
I've been told that every time a cd is released, I'm invited to join the company, so I've been living for that.
Please tell me how you feel about being able to sing!
Well, I don't know, but I never thought I would be able to perform in Ibaraki Prefecture, and there were so many big artists there today,
I never thought I would be able to perform in Ibaraki Prefecture, and there were so many big artists here today, so even when I was walking around, I could hear some of my favorite songs that I had heard before. I am very happy to be able to perform today. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. I wonder if there is only one other person among the 10 who has memories of Ibaraki.
It's bad, it's bad, it's bad, it's bad. It's a little bit bad.
So what do you think? How's it feel to be here for the first time? How do you feel now? I know it was raining.
Of course it was. I'm from Tochigi, too.
It's so close!
Yes, we're close.
I'm often told that I look like Namari, and I tell people I'm fine, but if I look like someone from Ibaraki, I get comments from fans when I'm distributing.
I get comments from fans when I deliver my messages.
They don't get along with each other because they live next door to each other.
Is that so?
No? Tochigi and Ibaraki are okay?
No, they're fine. - Really?
Really?
Yes.
I've never cared about Ichihara's attractiveness. I've never thought that Tochigi is low.
Tochigi has Nikko, after all. But really, we've been touring for a while, and this is the first time we've come to Ibaraki.
It was the first time for us to come to Ibaraki, so we are very happy to be here for such a big show.
I see. It's what you've always wanted to do. It's big. I've always wanted to perform, so I think the opening act is a very important part of the show.
I think it was the hardest part of the show.
I think it was the most difficult part. It was very exciting, wasn't it?
I think it was the hardest part of the show. You just made your debut, right?
That's right. It's still a ways to go.
It will soon be our second anniversary, and at first I wondered if it would be all right because there were no customers.
At the time of your debut?
This morning was a bit...
Before the show started, I wondered if it would be okay because it was raining.
But when I went out to the concert, there were so many fans there, and that little antique collector was there, and he was so excited to see me on top of his father, I thought it was a festival.
I felt like it was a festival.
Takarazuka Addisco, do you have more male or female fans?
They're all really supportive...
There are a lot of women who support us.
I'm very grateful.
They all came to the show today.
Even the women.
Women?
Female?
There you go.
Please don't do that.
You're out. You're out. You grew up here.
You're out! You're out!
I'm so glad.
The women wore their hair all back, too.
All back?
She wore her hair all back.
He looked so cool.
I was so happy to see that.
Oh, I see.
I guess it's like you all became idols because you liked it so much in the first place.
Now that we've become idols ourselves, we're the ones that everyone is looking up to.
We're not there yet, not at all.
Not yet!
It's not enough, right?
It's not enough yet!
Are there any artists you want to enjoy or see after this festival?
There are a lot of them.
I really want to eat.
I just saw the food menu for the artists backstage.
It looked really delicious, so I want to eat there.
I want to eat rice.
What do you like, by the way?
What? I like...
Food...
Do you want to introduce yourself?
No, I don't.
What's your favorite food?
Sea eel?
Conger eel.
I don't have any.
It's not on the menu.
No sea eel.
Curry...
There was curry!
I wanted curry.
I wanted to eat Bean-curd soup.
Oh, there was...
Yes, there was.
Only the sea eel was missing.
Damn!
Please prepare the sea eel again.
It's me.
Don't tell me...
I'm a hired MC too. I'm in a position where I could fly away if I blow.
I don't know, but I'm sure we'll have some food afterwards.
Are there any artists you'd like to see? I'm a little concerned about today.
I could hear the rehearsal of Huiyi Ishizaki.
I heard Ishizaki Hyui's rehearsal, but I wanted to go so much I almost skipped the interview.
I was about to skip the interview because I wanted to go to the concert so much.
Shall we end soon?
Yeah, yeah...
But since you weren't here, I'm already at Ganza.
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure.
I missed you so much. So much. Really? Me? For me?
Thank you. Thank you for the T-shirt.
Thank you very much. I'm sorry, I'm talking about Lucky Face, not Lucky Face.
I'm talking about something other than a lucky face, but... our dressing room is right in the middle of all the other venues.
We can hear the music of many artists. We're on the performers' side.
We were talking about how we want to go here now, looking at the timetable all the time.
So everyone is different? What do you like? Like bands?
But I want to see Kiss of Life. I love K-pop idols.
Yes, they're here. They're here. And they're backstage two doors down.
Two doors down from each other.
Is it possible? I was so excited.
I've been so excited since this morning.
If you put them on the wall like this...
You're pretty close.
I'll just kiss the wall for now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're a sought-after idol, too.
Not at all.
You're really cute.
Is there anyone else you'd like to see?
Maybe someone you haven't talked to yet.
If you don't mind.
I'm personally interested in seeing the new school leaders.
Nadeshiko from Koya.
Nadeshiko from Takano is making her major label debut with Mr. Entertainment.
We belong to the same company, so we're seniors.
I really wanted to see them live today.
I'm sure there are a lot of people like that today.
Leaders, right?
They're on fences all over the world, aren't they?
Yes, they are.
But...
You want to be like that, don't you?
No, do you want to be like that? Yes, I do! I just get so excited when I imagine it.
I see. Well, then, I hope all of you enjoy today's show.
Now, I would like to end with a message to all the people who came to the live show and are watching this video.
Can the representative speak?
Then, I will speak. Well, then, please do so.
Thank you for watching us.
It was a dream come true to be able to perform at the Lucky Fest today, so I was very happy and thank you so much for joining us in the rain and making our voices so loud and exciting.
We will do our best to perform on a bigger stage, so please continue to support us.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much for your support. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.